I knew he wouldn't pay up easily
Glad I swapped it with water beforehand
Mom, Dad
Lewes, no matter what
they are your elders after all
Calm them down first
If someone actually dies
you'll be in huge trouble
Spit it out, now
Stay back
Lewes, I'm begging you
Save my parents
Mom, Dad
Calm down, both of you
I'll pay, just toss the medicine
Go get your stomachs pumped now
No, give me the money first
Daniel, are you even human
Paraquat is lethal
One sip is all it takes
Just for money
you'd ignore your parents' lives
That's on you too
You should've paid sooner
Right, money first
What if you change your mind
Why do I feel nauseous
Fine, no time for cash
I'll transfer the money
Should've just agreed earlier
Wasting my time
Money, I finally have the money
Finally got it, let's go
The sun's making me dizzy
I need to go sleep it off
Sandra
Oh no, the poison's kicking in
To the hospital, quick
Mom, Dad, what's wrong
Mom, Dad
Dad
With my sister here
Lewes won't ignore Mom and Dad
I can take this money and disappear